{
  "easy": [
    {
      "question": "What does 'be' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["être","etre"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'my name is' mean in French?",
      "answer": "je m'apelle"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'do' mean in French?",
      "answer": "faire"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'live' mean in French?",
      "answer": "vivre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'year' mean in French?",
      "answer": "ans"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'like' mean in French?",
      "answer": "aimer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'my name is' mean in French?",
      "answer": "je m'apelle"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'walk' mean in French?",
      "answer": "aller"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'have' mean in French?",
      "answer": "avoir"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'call' mean in French?",
      "answer": "appeler"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'hear' meanin French?",
      "answer": ["écouter","ecouter"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'play' mean in French?",
      "answer": "jouer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'eat' mean in French?",
      "answer": "manger"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'find' mean in French?",
      "answer": "trouver"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'say' mean in French?",
      "answer": "dire"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'house' mean in French?",
      "answer": "maison"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'cat' mean in French?",
      "answer": "chat"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'dog' mean in French?",
      "answer": "chien"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'yes' mean in French?",
      "answer": "oui"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'no' mean in French?",
      "answer": "non"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'thank you' mean in French?",
      "answer": "merci"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'one' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["un","une"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'two' mean in French?",
      "answer": "deux"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'three' mean in French?",
      "answer": "troi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'four' mean in French?",
      "answer": "quatre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'five' mean in French?",
      "answer": "cinq"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'six' mean in French?",
      "answer": "six"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'seven' mean in French?",
      "answer": "sept"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'eight' mean in French?",
      "answer": "huit"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'nine' mean in French?",
      "answer": "neuf"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'ten' mean in French?",
      "answer": "dix"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'eleven' mean in French?",
      "answer": "onze"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'twelve' mean in French?",
      "answer": "douze"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'green' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["vert","verte"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'yellow' mean in French?",
      "answer": "jaune"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'red' mean in French?",
      "answer": "rouge"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'blue' mean in French?",
      "answer": "bleu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'black' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["noir","noire"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'white' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["blanc","blanche"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'orange' mean in French?",
      "answer": "orange"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'grey' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["gris","grise"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'brown' mean in French?",
      "answer": "marron"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'drink' mean in French?",
      "answer": "boire"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'learn' mean in French?",
      "answer": "apprendre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'see' mean in French?",
      "answer": "voir"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'dress' mean in French?",
      "answer": "robe"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'pants' mean in French?",
      "answer": "pantalon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'shoes' mean in French?",
      "answer": "chaussures"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'shirt' mean in French?",
      "answer": "chemise"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'pencil' mean in French?",
      "answer": "crayon"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'street' mean in French?",
      "answer": "rue"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'music' mean in French?",
      "answer": "musique"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'write' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["écrire","ecrire"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'want' mean in French?",
      "answer": "vouloir"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'arrive' mean in French?",
      "answer": "arriver"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'change' mean in French?",
      "answer": "changer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'sleep' mean in French?",
      "answer": "dormir"
    }
  ],
 
  "medium": [
   {
      "question": "write 'avoir' 1.P in passe compose",
      "answer": "j'ai eu"
    },
    {
      "question": "write 'être' 1.P in passe compose",
      "answer": ["j'ai été","j'ai ete"]
    },
    {
      "question": "write 'aller' 1.P in passe compose (m)?",
      "answer": "je suis allé"
    },
    {
      "question": "write 'apprendre' 1.P in passe compose?",
      "answer": "j'ai appris"
    },
    {
      "question": "write 'voir' 1.P in passe compose",
      "answer": "j'ai vu"
    },
    {
      "question": "write 'faire' 1.P in passe compose",
      "answer": "j'ai fait"
    },
    {
      "question": "write 'dire' 1.P in passe compose",
      "answer": "j'ai dit"
    },
    {
      "question": "write 'boire' in 1.P passe compose",
      "answer": "j'ai bu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'happy birthday' mean in French?",
      "answer": "bon anniversaire"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'spider' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["araignee","araignée"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'Monday' mean in French?",
      "answer": "lundi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'Tuesday' mean in French?",
      "answer": "mardi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'Wednesday' mean in French?",
      "answer": "mercredi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'Thursday' mean in French?",
      "answer": "jeudi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'Friday' mean in French?",
      "answer": "vendredi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'Saturday' mean in French?",
      "answer": "samedi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'Sunday' mean in French?",
      "answer": "dimanche"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'autumn' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["l'automne","automne"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'spring' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["le printemps","printemps"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'summer' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["l'ete","l'été","ete","été"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'come' mean in French?",
      "answer": "venir"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'can' mean in French?",
      "answer": "pouvoir"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'know' mean in French?",
      "answer": "savoir"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": "xy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": "xy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": "xy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": "xy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": "xy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": "xy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": "xy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": "xy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": "xy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": "xy"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'die' mean in French?",
      "answer": "mourir"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'run' mean in French?",
      "answer": "courir"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'flee' mean in French?",
      "answer": "fuir"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'cry' mean in French?",
      "answer": "pleurer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'think' mean in French?",
      "answer": "penser"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'win' mean in French?",
      "answer": "gagner"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'teach' mean in French?",
      "answer": "enseigner"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'kiss' mean in French?",
      "answer": "embrasser"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'dance' mean in French?",
      "answer": "danser"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'sing' mean in French?",
      "answer": "chanter"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'xy' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["arrêter","arreter"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'call' mean in French?",
      "answer": "appeler"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you build the passe compose of a regular French verb?",
      "answer": ["finite verb form of être/avoir + particip passe","infinite verb form of ",""],
      "right": 1
      
    },
    {
      "question": "What does 'winter' mean in French?",
      "answer": ["hiver","l'hiver"]
    } 
  ],
  "hard": [
    {
      "question": "Who is a good boy",
      "answer": ["You. Yes you are.", "How the fuck should I know"],
      "right": 1
    }
  ]
}
